magellans.com 2013-11-03

# Privacy Policy | Magellan's Travel Supplies

## Your Privacy Rights and Our Online Privacy Policy

Magellan's Travel LLC takes the privacy and protection of your personal information seriously. We want you to know how we collect, use and protect information about our online customers and visitors to our website www.magellans.com ("Website").

### Your Consent

By using our Website, you consent to our using information, including personally identifiable information, that is collected or submitted as described in this online privacy policy. We may change or add to this privacy policy in our discretion without notice, so we encourage you to review it periodically.

This Privacy Policy is effective: (i) immediately for new customers; or (ii) on August 2, 2007 for existing customers.

## I. Information We Collect

### Information You Give Us

We receive and may store any information (including personally identifiable information) you enter on our Website or give to our Website in any other way. For example, we collect information you provide when you place an order, set up an account with us, post comments to our web-site, send us an e-mail, sign up for a catalog or e-mail, or call us, enter a sweepstakes, or enroll or participate in a club or service such as gift registries. This information may include:

  * Your name
  * Your primary mailing address, billing address and any other addresses you may decide to use
  * Your e-mail address
  * Your phone number
  * Your credit card number and information
  * A password of your choosing
  * We may also collect on, an optional basis, information about your gender, your fax number how you heard about us, or other marketing information

It may also include any other personal or preference information you provide to us, and information you submit about other people; for example, the name and address of a gift recipient.

### Information from Other Sources

We may obtain information about you from Magellan's catalog and/or retail stores. This may help improve the personalization of our service to you by providing better product recommendations or special offers that we think will interest you.

### Automatic Information

We receive and store certain types of information whenever you interact with our Website. For example, we use "cookies" like many other websites. Through cookies we obtain certain types of information when your web browser accesses our Website.

### What are "Cookies" and how do we use them?

Cookies are like virtual "sticky" notes with a unique identifier that we transfer to your computer through your web browser. Cookies allow us to provide features such as recommended and related products and storage of items in your cart between visits.

The "help" portion of the toolbar on most browsers will tell you how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to have the browser notify you when you receive a new cookie or how to disable cookies altogether. However, cookies allow you to take full advantage of some of our Website's best features, so we recommend that you leave them turned on. 

## II. How We May Use and Share Your Information

In general, personally identifiable information you submit to us is used by us to provide you with the products and/or services you ordered, to register you for our services, to respond to requests that you make, to improve our services to better tailor the features, performance and support of our products and services, and to offer you additional information, opportunities, and functionality. Except as otherwise stated in this Privacy Policy, we do not trade, rent, or share your personally identifiable information with third parties, unless you ask or authorize us to do so.

### The Magellan's Companies

We may share information we collect at our Website, including personally identifiable information, with our affiliated companies that operate Magellan's catalog and retail stores. We may use this information to offer you products and services that may be of interest to you via catalog and store mailings, e-mails or events. If you provide your e-mail address through our Website, stores or catalog, you may receive e-mails from us. If you do not want to receive marketing or promotional e-mails from us, please contact customerservice@Magellans.com. You may still receive select e-mails from us if you have requested them through one of our site services such as e-mail newsletters, Trip Reminders, Gift Reminders, or other site services you request. You can discontinue these e-mails by canceling your subscription to these services. Additionally, you will still receive order confirmation, order tracking and other transactional e-mails when you order online. If you do not want us to mail you anything to your physical address from our Website, stores or catalog, please contact [customerservice@Magellans.com](mailto:customerservice@Magellans.com).

### Carefully Selected Companies and Organizations

We may share your name and mailing address with carefully screened business partners and other organizations, which are not part of the Magellan's companies. These companies and organizations may use the information we share to provide travel-related mailings and other offers to you.

If you do not want us to share information you provide to our Website with vendors, business partners and other organizations that are not part of the Magellan's companies, please contact [customerservice@Magellans.com](mailto:customerservice@Magellans.com). Because catalogs are planned and produced well before they are received the effect is not immediate when you request your name not be shared.

### Your California Privacy Rights 

If you do not want us to share information you provide to our Website with vendors, business partners and other organizations that are not part of Magellan's, please submit your request in writing to [customerservice@magellans.com](mailto:customerservice@magellans.com) or call 1–800–962-4943.

You may also contact us via mail: 

     Magellan's Customer Service
     16401 E 33rd Drive Suite 10
      Aurora, CO 80011

Because catalogs are planned and produced well before they are received the effect is not immediate when you request your name not be shared.

### Service Provider

Our Website may also share information, including personally identifiable information, with companies that provide support services to us (such as a printer, mailing house or web host) or that help us market our products and services to best provide for our customers. These companies may need information about you in order to perform their functions. These companies are not authorized to use the information we share with them for any other purpose.

### Protection of Our Website and Others

We may disclose information you provide to our Website, including personally identifiable information, when we believe disclosure is appropriate to comply with the law; to enforce or apply our Conditions of Use and other agreements; or to protect the rights, property or safety of our Website, our users or others.

### Business Transfers

If some or all of the business assets of our Website are sold or transferred, we generally would transfer the corresponding information regarding our guests. We also may retain a copy of that guest information.

### More Information

Please call 1–800–962-4943 or [contact us](mailto:customerservice@magellans.com) if you have further questions about our e-mail unsubscribe process.

## III. Other Questions and Security

### What about links to and from other websites?

Our Website may offer links to other sites. Other sites have their own policies regarding privacy. If you visit one of these sites, we recommend that you review the privacy policy on that site. In addition, you may have linked to our Website through another site. For example, in certain cases you may have linked to magellans.com through banner advertising on another site. In such cases the site you linked from may collect information from people who click on the banner or link. You may want to refer to the privacy policies on those sites to see how they collect and use this information.

### Children

We do not intentionally collect on the Website or maintain information from those visitors of our services who are under 13 years old.

### Security

### Our Commitment to Data Security

We have industry standard physical, electronic and procedural security safeguards that are intended to protect and secure the information we collect.

### Secure Sockets Layering (SSL)

Our Website uses Secure Sockets Layering (SSL) to encrypt your personal credit information, including your credit card number, before it travels over the Internet. SSL technology is the industry standard for secure online transactions.

### Safe Shopping 

Our security measures are designed to prevent anyone from stealing and using your credit card number. In addition, consumer protection laws protect you against the unauthorized use of your credit card. Under the Fair Credit Billing Act, if your credit card is used without your authorization, your liability for those fraudulent charges cannot exceed $50. So, if someone steals your credit card or your credit card number, your liability is limited to $50 no matter how much the thief charges to your account. If your credit card provider does hold you liable for any part of this $50, we will cover the entire liability for you, up to the full $50.

We will cover this liability only if the unauthorized use of your credit card resulted through no fault of your own from purchases made at our Website while using the secure server. In the event of unauthorized use of your credit card, you must notify your credit card provider in accordance with its reporting rules and procedures.

### LAST UPDATED Feb, 2013

July, 2007 – Re-written and added Magellan's Travel LLC as a member of the Magellan's companies.
